question_data = [
            {
                "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "question": "Snakes and Ladders was originally created in India?",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "Entertainment: Film",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "question": "Han Solo&#039;s co-pilot and best friend, &quot;Chewbacca&quot;, is an Ewok.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "Geography",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "question": "San Marino is the only country completely surrounded by another country.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "Geography",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "question": "There is a city called Rome in every continent on Earth.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "question": "Bill Cipher in the show &quot;Gravity Falls&quot; is the good guy.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "General Knowledge",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "History",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "question": "Adolf Hitler was tried at the Nuremberg trials.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": "Politics",
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "question": "Former president Theodore Roosevelt (1900-1908)  ran for another term under the Progressive Party in 1912.",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            }
]